### KARTIK SHAH

kartik.isworking@gmail.com | +61 404 874 569

https://ikartiks.github.io/ | https://github.com/ikartiks | https://in.linkedin.com/in/ikartiks

## **Summary of Experience**

I have 7.5 years of experience in various domains like Banking (core domain off lately), digital marketing & healthcare. My core forte is Android, but I have worked on both frontend and backend using technologies like Angular JS, Spring & Hibernate. I have also worked on NoSqI technologies like CouchDb which offers in built sync mechanism with conflict resolution. I provide end to end Omni channel experience to clients as per requirements. I like building products. Love to teach & learn. Looking for an opportunity at New South Wales, Australia (State sponsored PR holder).

### Education

Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology, Mumbai University, 2011

#### Certifications

Google & Udacity's Android Developer Nanodegree, Udacity's Self Driving Car Nanodegree (Ongoing)

## **Technical Skills**

Strong: Android, Kotlin, BackBase, CouchDB, Building voice actions with Home

Knowledgeable: Angular JS, Spring, JPA, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, SQL, Oracle, Python, Machine Learning, core PHP, RXJava /RXKotlin,

observables

Methodology: Agile using Jira & Pivotal Tracker, SCRUM, Kanban boards.

Tools: Jenkins for Continues integration, Burp Suite for network security, J-meter for load testing, GIT for version control.

### Work Experience -

## Apr 2019 - Present, Frollo (Volt Bank / Labs) Sydney, Australia

- I work on an app for Volt bank called Volt Labs, build on top of the Frollo SDK, so my major chunk of work here includes having an aesthetic UI.
- Built certain important chunks of Frollo SDK like Transactions, partially worked on Frollo app.
- Worked on Volt Banks main app mainly on Cards module and fixing bugs for various other modules.

### Jan 2019 - April 2019, Telstra via Luvo (contract). Sydney, Australia

Working on Telstra's 24x7 app. I worked mainly on their messaging module, as well as redesigning the app modules.

Indian Experience - 6 years (For complete Indian experience view detailed resume.)

# OCT 2015 – OCT 2018, Tata Consultancy Services. IT Analyst, Mumbai

- Leading a team of 7 developers to build a Banking application (HDFC). App has 10M+ installs & 3.9 \* rating.
- Built a hybrid app using phonegap for Sony Picture Entertainment's Digital windows project.
- Built, developed websites (backend and frontend) for Sony Picture Entertainment's SmartR project, SOAR

## **Major Projects**

Frollo	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=us.frollo.frollo.prod https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=au.com.voltbank.voltlabs.prod	Kotlin, LiveData, TDD Same Tech stack
	https://www.voltbank.com.au/	Nav components / RX / Databinding
Telstra 24x7	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.telstra.mobile.android.mytelstra	Kotlin, RxJava / RxKotlin, TDD
HDFC Bank	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.snapwork.hdfc	Android, Backbase, Kotlin
Vocabulary Flashcards	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.kartik.grevocab	Android, Kotlin (my product)
YRD Health app	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.yrdtechnologies	Android, Kotlin (in beta request access)
EPMWare	http://epmware.com/	Spring, Hibernate, JPA, AngularJS
Dr. Fixit	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pidilite.drfixit	Hybrid app development
Team Tracker	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.graymatrix.teamtracker	Android, Couch database
USL's RCB IPL Team	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.royalchallengers.android	Android, core JS, PHP
USL's Signature Selfies app	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.usl.signatureselfies	Android, core JS, PHP
Britania's iHealthU	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ihealthu.program.challenge	Android, core JS, PHP
Adlabs Imagica	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.adlabs.themepark	Android, core JS, PHP
Castrol Cricket	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.castrolcricket.android	Android, core JS, PHP
EC Diwali cracker app	https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.experiencecommerce.android	Android, core JS, PHP
Awards & Leadership		

- Complete sponsorship to Google's Android Career summit Bangalore 2016 for top 50 selected Android developers across India.
- Complete sponsorship to Mobile developer summit held in Bangalore 2013.
- Complete sponsorship to Udacity & Google's Android Developer Nanodegree course.
- Best team award at TCS, Client appreciation across multiple projects.